Contact

7134474889 (Mobile) tlketner@me.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tabathaketner-56a26841 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Registered Nurses

Nursing

Healthcare

Certifications

Certified Post Anesthesia Nurse (CPAN)

Tabatha Ketner

Nurse Educator at Houston Methodist

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing from Liberty University.

Experience

Houston Methodist

14 years 1 month

Nurse Educator

November 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Houston, Texas

Critical Care RN

April 2015 - Present (5 years 3 months)

Post Anesthesia Care of patients following ENT, Opthamology, AV, and Plastics related surgery.

Registered Nurse

June 2006 - Present (14 years 1 month)

Shiloh Treatment Ctr Director Of Nursing Services April 2016 - March 2018 (2 years)

UTMB

Registered Nurse

October 2010 - January 2012 (1 year 4 months)

Bridge Staffing

Travel RN June 2008 - December 2008 (7 months) Conroe Regional Medical Center

Christus VNA Home Health Hospice RN October 2007 - May 2008 (8 months)

Education

Liberty University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing · (2014 - June 2017)

San Jacinto College Associate Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2003 - 2006)

Houston Community College